<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SwissTool</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_title">HOME FRAGMENT</string>
    <string name="alphabet_viewer_title">ALPHABET VIEWER</string>
    <string name="stress_tapper_viewer_title">STRESS TAPPER</string>
    <string name="birth_stones_title">BIRTH STONES</string>
    <string name="stone_detail_title">BIRTH STONE DETAIL</string>
    <string name="alphabet">Alphabet</string>
    <string name="tapper">Tapper</string>
    <string name="stones">Stones</string>
    <string name="layout_switch">switch</string>
    <string name="click">Click</string>
    <string name="garnet">JANUARY,AQUARIUS, GARNET STONE
Garnets are a group of silicate minerals that have been used since the Bronze Age as gemstones and abrasives.</string>
    <string name="amethyst">FEBRUARY,PICSIS, AMETHYST
A violet variety of quartz, the ancient Greeks wore amethyst and carved drinking vessels from it in the belief that it would prevent intoxication.</string>
    <string name="bloodstone">MARCH, ARIES, BLOODSTONE
The red inclusions are supposed to resemble spots of blood, hence the name bloodstone. The name heliotrope derives from various ancient notions about the manner in which the mineral reflects light.</string>
    <string name="diamond">APRIL, TAURUS, DIAMOND
Commonly, natural sapphires are cut and polished into gemstones and worn in jewelry.</string>
    <string name="agate">MAY, GEMINI, AGATE
Although agates may be found in various kinds of host rock, they are classically associated with volcanic rocks and can be common in certain metamorphic rocks.</string>
    <string name="emerald">JUNE, CANCER, EMERALD
Emeralds, like all colored gemstones, are graded using four basic parameters–the four Cs of connoisseurship: color, clarity, cut and carat weight.</string>
    <string name="onyx">JULY, LEO, ONYX
Onyx primarily refers to the parallel banded variety of the silicate mineral chalcedony.</string>
    <string name="carnelian">AUGUST, VIRGO, CARNELIAN
Carnelian (also spelled cornelian[2]) is a brownish-red mineral commonly used as a semi-precious gemstone.</string>
    <string name="chrysolite">SEPTEMBER, LIBRA, CHRYSOLITE
Peridot is one of the few gemstones that occur in only one color: an olive-green.</string>
    <string name="beryl">OCTOBER, SCORPIO, BERYL
Pure beryl is colorless, but it is frequently tinted by impurities; possible colors are green, blue, yellow, red (the rarest), and white. Beryl is also an ore source of beryllium.</string>
    <string name="topaz">NOVEMBER, SAGITTARIUS, TOPAZ
Topaz crystallizes in the orthorhombic system, and its crystals are mostly prismatic terminated by pyramidal and other faces.</string>
    <string name="ruby">DECEMBER, CAPRICORN, RUBY
The quality of a ruby is determined by its color, cut, and clarity, which, along with carat weight, affect its value.</string>
</resources>
